how many few ladies have a husband that
snores raise your arm Mona help you out
what are you looking at yeah don't do
that don't be scared are your wife so
that's not your wife oh okay ladies
admit it if your husband's swords say
something I have an aunt who died from
secondhand sleep apnea it will kill you
men don't admit it no I don't snore and
like hey 200 likes on Facebook I taped
you last night men don't understand that
this woman they married was one day
going I would love to marry a prince and
we're not gonna sleep at night anymore
we're gonna catch up and talk and talk
and listen to music and then you get
married wedding night at midnight he's
but you still madly in love you go oh my
honey nice oxygen test your head honey
bun you're making a little noises two
years Larry you still have not slept
since wedding night
he's still but now your attitude have
changed look at him look up and saying
just take him Moses killed an Egyptian
and you forgave him let's just call it a
pillow fight that went wrong five years
later you know all girls sleep in bed
next to him you're just standing there
staring at him I don't respect you look
at you you oxygen hawk you suck the roof
in you inhale and you start treating him
like a dog roll over roll over
lay down ten years later he has the
machine now go I should have listened to
my mother she knew something was wrong
with him
fifteen years later he's older drooling
hair on the throw like just go here's
your sacrifice just take him I'm done
send me to India I'll do any work just
what does he sound like bad some of them
sound like a harley-davidson the nice
tune up honey put a nutria on trying to
sleep some sound like a lion facing a
hummingbird it'd be so scary that we
wake up we have a mortgage wake up now
in this economy you're not leaving
good one I don't know why I don't sir
from the Malays with like Jewish people
it's not when we talk hi how are you and
my wife doesn't snore either so we hear
every noise that happens downstairs we
have a fridge that waits for us I know
it to go to bed and the ice cubes will
go boom and my wife would go what is
that I go I don't know I guess care to
you know what I mean she goes go down
and check it's your turn I went the last
time but you're the man what if it's a
female burger so one time I was doing
the Grand Ole Opry in Nashville
Tennessee home of country music couples
America and after the show they gave me
this suite at the Opryland be too big
pets forgot to book a room for my road
manager and the crew and I go over to
the road manager said hey I have an
extra bed because know you're the artist
I'm like come on so he's older he's
sleeping I'm sleeping I wake up to hear
someone cutting a tree and eating
Doritos at the same time
all night so I put my headphones on I
put it on Drake and rap it's a lot of
thing I could come up with it didn't
have those like
[Applause]
so I took my pill I said I'm gonna choke
him a little bit so I get close to him
he started dreaming out loud oh they're
coming open the door
start the car oh the car won't start all
I wanted to choke him but I want to hear
the end of the story I'm neither thank
you so much hey did you know that Drybar
comedy has their own app download it
right now and watch save and share clips
and watch my whole special too